<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Reunions 2025</title><description></description><link>https://keepitfun.biz</link><atom:link
    href="https://keepitfun.biz/feed.rss"
    rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"
/><language>en</language><generator>Ignite v0.2.1</generator><image><url>https://reunions.princeton2000.org/images/rss.png</url><title>Reunions 2025</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz</link><width>144</width><height>152</height></image><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/registration/early%2520registration</guid><title>early registration</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/registration/early%2520registration</link><description><![CDATA[Early registration will run through December 31, 2024.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[registration]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Early registration will run through December 31, 2024.</strong></p><p><strong>Please register early!</strong> The more certainty we have around attendance, the more budget we can commit to making sure you and your guests have a great time.</p><p><strong>What’s Included:</strong></p><ul><li>All meals are included in registration.</li><li>All participants will receive a T-shirt, and each classmate will receive a canvas tote bag, bandana, and a commemorative pin.</li><li>Additional swag (hats, umbrellas, etc.) will be available for purchase through the year.</li></ul><p><strong>Notes:</strong></p><ul><li><strong>Jacket orders MUST be received by December 13, 2024.</strong></li><li>Some swag may not be available for late registrants.</li><li>Depending on demand, we <em>may</em> do a follow-on order <em>after</em> Reunions for those who missed out and want their 25th jacket for future Princeton events.</li><li>Jackets are a separate purchase from Reunions Registration. Even if you can’t make Reunions, <em>you <strong>can</strong> still buy a jacket!</em></li></ul><!--*Check-in hours are at our 25th Reunion HQ in the Whitman College upper courtyard.*-->
<!---->
<!--**Hours**-->
<!--* **Thursday:** Noon – 11:00 pm-->
<!--* **Friday:** 9:00 am – Midnight-->
<!--* **Saturday:** 9:00 am – Midnight-->
<p>Questions? Please email the <a href="mailto:gia.fruscione@gmail.com">Registration Chair</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/template</guid><title>template</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/template</link><description><![CDATA[Like many of the thousands of people at the Great Lakes Science Center on Monday, eclipse glasses in hand, Josh Pepper waited patiently for the moment when all eyes shifted to the sky. He answered questions about the eclipse and science at the NASA Village at the science center. The reverence for the topic shined through his genuine smile and hearty laugh.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Class Letters]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like many of the thousands of people at the Great Lakes Science Center on Monday, eclipse glasses in hand, Josh Pepper waited patiently for the moment when all eyes shifted to the sky. He answered questions about the eclipse and science at the NASA Village at the science center. The reverence for the topic shined through his genuine smile and hearty laugh.</p><p>After years of study, Josh said he is doing what excites him the most.</p><p><a href="https://www.ideastream.org/community/2024-04-09/two-generations-of-nasa-scientists-share-their-love-and-their-knowledge-during-eclipse">More at Ideastream</a></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/registration_week</guid><title>registration_week</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/registration_week</link><description><![CDATA[Hello 2000, and welcome to WhatsApp! I am thrilled to announce that thanks to the incredible work of your Reunions Committee, we are ahead of schedule, and started beta testing registration on Thursday! I wanted to give you all a rundown so you know what to expect this week.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Registration Week]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hello 2000, and welcome to WhatsApp! I am thrilled to announce that thanks to the incredible work of your Reunions Committee, we are ahead of schedule, and started beta testing registration on Thursday! I wanted to give you all a rundown so you know what to expect this week.</p><p>We’d love some additional testing from this group, particularly those of you who are international. Don’t worry, even if you don’t know exactly who’s going to be in your group, you can edit your registration later. If you’re interested, we can take 20-30 people tomorrow. Just message me here, and I’ll pass along the link.</p><p>Depending on feedback, we’ll open registration to this group on Wednesday or Thursday.</p><p>Friday, we’ll send a class-wide email with the theme and jacket design and open up registration.</p><p>One very important point is that registration is separate from your class jacket order. Registration runs until May, but with the lead times we need for the jacket, your jacket order must be in by DECEMBER 13. That is very, very soon. The jacket team made an awesome sizing chart that you can find <a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org/images/jacket/P2000_25th_Jacket_Sizing_Chart.pdf">here:</a> You can print it out and take it to a tailor or have a friend help. It’s quick, but it does appear to best be done as a two-person job.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/housing_update</guid><title>housing_update</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/housing_update</link><description><![CDATA[Class Survey]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[housing]]></category><category><![CDATA[survey]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Class Survey</strong></p><p>We have a quick survey for you to help with logistics and orders around Reunions next year. We want to get a sense of the who, where, when, and how (we’re pretty clear on the what and why). If you have plans, let us know them. If you don’t have plans, let’s start the conversation!<a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScONM_ALtuH8QFf9Ztr09NxkplNSlDDsdwJXBZy_2vpWs6o-w/viewform">TAKE THE SURVEY</a></p><p><strong>HOUSING UPDATE</strong></p><p>Hey gang, wanted to get to you all with an update on housing, mostly because Nassau Inn kicks off the frenzy by opening up their reservation window tomorrow (Weds) at 10am ET.</p><p>With the demands of Reunions, housing is a mix of on-campus housing, local hotels, and room available through friendly institutions (e.g. Rider University), not to mention Airbnbs and short-term rentals like that. Here’s a quick overview.</p><p><strong>On-Campus Housing</strong></p><p>The University administers on-campus housing, which you can sign up for when you register for Reunions. It’s not 100% guaranteed – it depends on how many undergrads stay on campus through Reunions – but it is pretty reliably available for major reunions like ours. It is definitely the cheapest option, typically about $150 for a bed for the weekend, but 1) it can be anywhere on campus (potentially without AC), 2) you’ll have a shared bathroom, and 3) you’ll need to provide your own linens (This may be less of an issue as the ‘99s found a rental service to take care of this. We’ll probably use it, but we still need to set that up). Also, the University tries to keep all members of a party together, but can’t promise it.</p><p><strong>Local Hotels</strong></p><p>We have currently reserved about <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1chWYFV69EQlY-L3wMB8wqE0hravAz8YuFYw_Y0W5qkk/edit?gid=0#gid=0">210 rooms</a> across 11 hotels in the area. Most of them were on this year’s Reunions shuttle bus route to and from campus, and most are along Route 1. We’re still gathering booking links to make those reservations, but rates are coming in between $290 and $550 a night, and we have a good mix of bed/occupancy types. We have a <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1chWYFV69EQlY-L3wMB8wqE0hravAz8YuFYw_Y0W5qkk/edit?gid=0#gid=0">list</a> of local hotels here. We note where we have a group rate, and list the mix of what’s available. Most of the hotels in the area are opening reservations over the next month or so, so this is a living document. The two hotels right downtown, open booking tomorrow. Expect the Nassau Inn to sell out in a couple of hours. The Graduate Hotel is new to the area, and just opened on Nassau Street across from the Rocky dining hall. We’ve been talking to them for 14 months off and on about room blocks, and, well…we wish them and their proposed room rates all the success in the world.</p><p><strong>Friendlies</strong></p><p>We’re still reaching out to the local institutions - Rider College, Westminster Choir College, and Princeton Theological Seminary. They tend to open up later on in the process. Based on the ’99s experience this year, the pricing is a little more than on campus, but they have AC, linens are included, and are on the shuttle route, so a decent value overall.</p><p><strong>Airbnb, Vrbo etc.</strong></p><p>A lot of locals are willing to rent their homes out during Reunions, even some otherwise loyal alumni during an off-year (We missed you this year, Ann!). That inventory can certainly vary and outside of the committee’s domain, but it’s worth checking out as well.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/theme_poll</guid><title>theme_poll</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/theme_poll</link><description><![CDATA[Dear ‘00 Classmates,]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[theme]]></category><category><![CDATA[poll]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dear ‘00 Classmates,</p><p>Our 25th Reunion is now less than a year away, and your volunteer organizers are in high gear selecting a theme and design elements.  The purpose of this message is (1) to provide an update on theme and jacket planning, and (2) to invite you to provide feedback on ideas.</p><p>25th Reunion Costume</p><p>As you may recall from Reunions, the centerpiece of the 25th will be a new Reunions jacket.  This blazer is a more formal upgrade from the beer jacket we received at graduation, and classmates typically continue to wear their 25th blazers at future Reunions and other alumni events.  There will be other pieces to our 25th Reunion look, please stay tuned!</p><p>The blazer will be a separate purchase from your registration fee, and classmates will be given the opportunity to order 25th blazers whether or not they are able to attend the 25th in person.  You’ll hear from us in the fall about ordering and sizing details.</p><p>25th Reunion Theme</p><p>After having our 20th canceled due to COVID, classmate feedback ahead of our 25th is clear: We are hearing that you want “high attendance,” “broad participation,” and “to focus on being together.”  Your Reunions volunteers – more than 30 strong so far – fully agree!</p><p>We have also been told by some of you that the overall feel of our Reunion is more important than the specific theme, and we have heard words like “classic,” “fun,” “classy,” and “good looking jacket.”</p><p>Taking into account theme suggestions from classmates, general concepts informed by previous classes’ 25th experience, and University guidelines for Reunions themes, the relevant committees have met several times to brainstorm and develop workable ideas for our 25th Reunion theme.  And now we are ready to hear from you once again…</p><p><a href="http://url1707.princeton.edu/uni/ls/click?upn=u001.n3nnp8OSNP2-2FHbo-2F-2BocdbK45Md2EorqhbNVmS4IOlKWz2pLVtZDTK5VV5TDxbocgPfmsg7QnymwQp00GECGdX-2B52I6JLSy0hGc63VX5gtvW8BeWXzB6OlA38ek-2FfPnmvNbFhKom95uSCzXRCZhLTZK8oc-2BITfpfS-2FR92HKonARg-3DJjxX_RNtWHZlvBOgdhx1h3dB6K7OWLj-2B8iTpXZeK8qIx1OVVqfkLQhoz-2BRJ5uq6VxyJtYKEQc2KJJ90mTtvf-2B-2FMFemMxUom474kwepPkJAAYfKSsL-2BlIjWBWlnMm9qTzvGHoO5051UM5HL4lg2AENpgir8dENGbSOoFsol3hm0TeQaopruPD-2B9C5YmEJXq6I7wxv-2FEo4Lkb5K2KepzQwm6Q5tSbOo8F7q1X5MuLvp0EMfPcE4ccLi1sfbJqyTuDZz-2BDcSPS2onFuPDOFF9pYy1ii5pyiO9iW6YPCmU9WmrYzov9ekOHtq8DKXWopHfQb5B-2BQndtHUAAj5nCH3K1c0KX-2B0AZDDIKHUZkoebvD0oSCR6awEAVIZ-2FHn4zXrUAD-2FmNexX2YtyRN-2BD9dtPlQSYZFpXzMiSMFSznSMUUl06ojHDjgpDRuUxEPNIA4uwiRLZJNX9-2FsYfKt9y1zz302D-2FwCkSwXzJKa1n3WPvc3KotY-2FuDko-3D">Give us your feedback!</a></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/classLetter0824</guid><title>classLetter0824</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/classLetter0824</link><description><![CDATA[Dear Classmate,]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Class Letter]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dear Classmate,</p><p>Yes!</p><p>Sorry, I had to try that out…what a thrill! Hope you felt it too. Really, this letter is meant to catch you up with what’s going on with your dear Class of 2000 as we gear up for our 25th Reunion, <strong>May 22-25, 2025</strong>. Email has been unreliable, so we’re going old school to make sure you have the most important information now and know how to stay in touch through the year.</p><p>There are three things to remember:</p><p>•	<a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org">reunions.princeton2000.org</a> is the source of truth</p><p>•	Registration opens <strong>November 1</strong></p><p>•	Please join our WhatsApp broadcast channel <a href="https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements">here:</a></p><p><strong>Reunions Site – <a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org">reunions.princeton2000.org</a></strong></p><p>The most important thing to remember is <a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org">reunions.princeton2000.org</a>. That is the source of truth for all Reunions information going forward. The site has information on housing, schedule, kids’ activities, and frequently asked questions. Some things, like the schedule, are still developing, so check for updates throughout the year.</p><p><strong>Registration – November 1</strong></p><p>Our 25th Reunion will be May 22-25, 2025. That is <strong>the most important date on your calendar</strong> going forward. Just make sure you’re in Princeton those days, and everything else will pretty much work out for you. That said, the second-most important date is <strong>November 1, 2024</strong>, when we open registration.</p><p>Anyway, you can <strong>go to <a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org">reunions.princeton2000.org</a> on November 1</strong>. We’d really appreciate it if you can register early. The more certainty we have around attendance, the more budget we can commit to our entertainment, food, and beverages. You know you’re coming to Reunions (<em>we all know</em> you’re coming to Reunions)…so register early!</p><p><strong>Communications – <a href="https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements">join our WhatsApp</a></strong></p><p>It seems that only about 60% of you are receiving our emails, and it’s a different 60% each time. If you haven’t received our emails, I’m really sorry about that. We’re trying to address it in three ways.</p><p>First, if you set up forwarding to your real email years ago via an @alumni address, that’s a source of a lot of our problems. Best to go to Tigernet and update the directory to reflect your actual email account.</p><p>Second, while emails from Tigernet don’t seem to deliver, emails from a personal account seem to arrive simply fine. I’m happy to send them again to you on the side. Just drop me an email at jpurnell@alumni and I’ll put you on my list.</p><p>Third, we’ve set up a channel on WhatsApp that will be used for official class announcements. It is not a group chat, just a way for us to broadcast out key information. As a side benefit, it will allow us to get information out quickly during Reunions if we need to adjust anything on the fly. Please  visit <a href="https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements">https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements</a> to join.</p><p><strong>Recap</strong></p><p>•	Right now: <a href="https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements">https://bit.ly/P2000Announcements</a>.</p><p>•	<strong>November 1:</strong> Registration: <a href="https://reunions.princeton2000.org">reunions.princeton2000.org</a>.</p><p>•	<strong>May 22-25:</strong> You, Reunions, Princeton.</p><p>Tiger, Tiger Tiger,</p><p>Justin</p><p>P.S. you look great, everybody loves you, and we all simply can’t <em>wait</em> to see you at Reunions.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/letters/time_to_roar</guid><title>time_to_roar</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/letters/time_to_roar</link><description><![CDATA[Reunions 2024 – History!]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[reunions2024]]></category><category><![CDATA[volunteering]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Reunions 2024 – History!</strong></p><p>Reunions 2024…in a books and a major success! Congratulations to the ‘99s on an excellent weekend. But as we all know…it was but a prelude. We’re up! Reunions 2025 runs from Thursday, May 22 through Saturday, May 24th. Mark your calendars! We’ll have a steady drumbeat of information starting this summer as we run up to the big date, but one thing I know people are wondering about is housing. We’re getting blocks at most hotels at every price point, but one hotel that doesn’t do blocks for Reunions is the Nassau Inn. If you’re hoping to stay there, the Nassau Inn starts booking for Reunions 2025 on Wednesday, July 10, at 10am Eastern Time. I think the rooms go very very quickly, so be at the ready.</p><p><strong>Reunions Committee Volunteering</strong></p><p>If you got the Reunions bug this weekend and want to make things happen for the class, the door is always open to volunteers. Send me an email, and fill out this google form so we know how to contact you!</p><p>🐅🐅🐅</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/colophon/colophon</guid><title>colophon</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/colophon/colophon</link><description><![CDATA[Type is in Libre Franklin]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[Colophon]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Type is in <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Libre+Franklin">Libre Franklin</a></p><p>Our Header is in <a href="https://oitstyleguide.princeton.edu/brand-and-marketing-guidelines/typography-and-fonts">Princeton Monticello</a></p><p>The Reunions Typeface is Taylor Penton’s <a href="https://www.taylorpenton.com/fonts/p/lennon">Lennon</a></p><p><strong>ESSENTIAL APPS</strong></p><p><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/xcode/id497799835?mt=12">XCode</a></p><p><a href="https://macromates.com">TextMate 2</a></p><p><strong>SERVER SOFTWARE</strong></p><p>The Princeton 2000 Reunions website is just a Github Pages site.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/dues/dues</guid><title>dues</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/dues/dues</link><description><![CDATA[What Are Class Dues and Why Are They Important?]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[dues]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li><strong>What Are Class Dues and Why Are They Important?</strong></li><li><strong>Goals for Class Dues</strong></li><li><strong>Dues Payers Receive Priority for On-campus Reunions Housing Deadline: December 15</strong></li></ul><p>As we ramp up for our 25th, we would like to enlist your support to keep our class finances strong and fund programs & events as we head into Reunions and beyond. Our class dues participation rates have been dropping over the last few years so we wanted to take a moment to explain why we collect dues and what exactly these funds go to support. Class dues cycle on a fiscal year basis (i.e., July 1 – June 30) and fund the obligations of the class and are separate from Annual Giving, which supports the University. Each year these expenses include:</p><ul><li><strong>Princeton Alumni Council (ALCO) Dues:</strong> Each class pays dues to the Alumni Council to fund its operations. ALCO is the official connector of the Alumni Community with the University and organizes all the amazing alumni events you’ve attended including Reunions, Alumni Day, and the highly-successful conferences such as She Roars and ¡Adelante Tigres!. In addition, ALCO connects regional associations and supports class operations.</li><li><strong>Technology, Printing and Mailing:</strong> As you might imagine, there are costs associated with maintaining the website and putting together communications to the class. While not substantial, these costs are recurring.</li><li><strong>Class Events and Community Service:</strong> In past years, our class has been able to support class gatherings in various cities and modestly support community service efforts. However, we’d like to be in a financial position to be able to do more on both fronts.</li><li><strong>Class dues are 100% tax deductible!</strong></li></ul><p><strong>Dues Goals:</strong>Our goal is to raise our dues participation rate and build class funds to support more class gatherings across the globe. We know you’re busy, and to make it easier, we’ve launched a variety of alternative dues payment plans. In addition to a simple one-time payment, we can now set up recurring annual payments, something many have asked for over the years. In addition, you can now set up a five-year advance payment option. Under this new structure, you can pay your dues with a 20% discount for this year and the next four to come so you can cross this action item off your list (at least until our 30th rolls around)! Finally, we’ve set up a one-time “lifetime” dues plan. If you’d like, you can make a one-time payment of…$2,000 and never worry about dues again! So there are now four options for paying your dues this fiscal year:</p><p><strong><a href="https://www.princeton2000.org/memberships">Pay your dues!</a></strong> <em>(requires Tigernet login)</em></p><ul><li><strong>Regular Dues:</strong>  <a href="https://www.princeton2000.org/memberships">$50/classmate</a></li><li><strong>Annual Dues:</strong> <a href="https://www.princeton2000.org/memberships">$50/classmate/year</a></li><li><strong>Five Year Prepayment Regular Dues:</strong> <a href="https://www.princeton2000.org/memberships">$200/classmate</a></li><li><strong>Lifetime Dues:</strong> <a href="https://www.princeton2000.org/memberships">$2,000/classmate</a></li></ul><p>Please consider donating at your earliest convenience and if you are unsure if you have paid your dues last year or this year, just email our treasurer.</p><p><strong>Dues Payers Receive Priority for On-Campus Reunions Housing</strong></p><p>The Reunions committee has been hard at work securing housing both on and off campus for our class. As a thank you to those classmates whose continued participation enables our class to operate, we will be giving classmates who have paid dues for this year and last (FY 2024-2025 and 2023-2024 respectively) priority in the on-campus housing lottery. In years past, on campus housing has been limited and oversubscribed. This year is expected to be the same. Please note: Beds will first be assigned via a lottery among all classmates who meet the dues payment requirement by December 15, 2024. If you have not paid your 2023-2024 dues yet, you will have the opportunity to pay these dues in arrears in order to qualify. Any beds not assigned in this preferential lottery will then be made available in a lottery to the rest of the class.</p><p><strong>For more 25th Reunion Housing details, including 2000 Hotel Blocks, please visit the Housing page</strong></p><p>Finally, our class relies on the updates you send in with your dues! Even just a line or two about a recent move, a new job or baby, or a mini-Reunion with old friends keeps our Class Notes column current and fresh with news from classmates you may not see on Facebook or other social media. All updates submitted either via snail mail or the P2000 website are read! And, of course, you can always email Morey.</p><p>Your ideas are always welcome. We hope to see you all in Tigertown this June for Reunions 2025 (May 22-25)!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/template</guid><title>template</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/template</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[template]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/wristband-requirement</guid><title>wristband-requirement</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/wristband-requirement</link><description><![CDATA[Wristbands are not necessary during events such as the P-rade and Fireworks. Please note that wristbands are only required to enter Reunion headquarter sites after 5 p.m. with the exception of class-only meals.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[on-campus]]></category><category><![CDATA[headquarters]]></category><category><![CDATA[wristbands]]></category><category><![CDATA[policy]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wristbands are not necessary during events such as the P-rade and Fireworks. Please note that wristbands are only required to enter Reunion headquarter sites after 5 p.m. with the exception of class-only meals.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/linen-rental-location</guid><title>linen-rental-location</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/linen-rental-location</link><description><![CDATA[If you pre-ordered linens (e.g. sheets, towels, blankets, and pillow) and are staying on-campus, they will be placed in your dorm room in advance of your arrival. When you depart, you will return your linen rentals to the registration table at Whitman College. Please confirm that a crew member marks your items as returned.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[check-in]]></category><category><![CDATA[linens]]></category><category><![CDATA[locations]]></category><category><![CDATA[housing]]></category><category><![CDATA[registration]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>If you pre-ordered linens (e.g. sheets, towels, blankets, and pillow) and are staying on-campus, they will be placed in your dorm room in advance of your arrival. When you depart, you will return your linen rentals to the registration table at Whitman College. Please confirm that a crew member marks your items as returned.</li><li>As a reminder, there will be a $50 charge per set of bed linens that are not properly returned at the conclusion of the event.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/jackets-multiple</guid><title>jackets-multiple</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/jackets-multiple</link><description><![CDATA[Absolutely! These things have to last a while.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[jacket]]></category><category><![CDATA[multiple jackets]]></category><category><![CDATA[post-reunions]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>Absolutely! These things have to last a while.</li></ul><!--- If you will not be attending Reunions, email [jacket czar](mailto:p2000jackets@gmail.com) after the planning team has had a chance to recover from the weekend, but before June 5, with the subject line “LATE JACKET ORDER.”-->
]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/housing-hotels</guid><title>housing-hotels</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/housing-hotels</link><description><![CDATA[Here is a list of local hotels that have historically been serviced by Reunions Shuttles.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[housing]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is a <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1chWYFV69EQlY-L3wMB8wqE0hravAz8YuFYw_Y0W5qkk/edit?gid=0#gid=0">list of local hotels</a> that have historically been serviced by Reunions Shuttles.</p><p>Limited on-campus housing will be allocated via lottery in mid-February. Those who receive beds will be emailed, and room assignments will be distributed by University housing representatives at check-in.</p><p>For those who indicate interest in on-campus housing but do not receive beds, an email will also be sent in mid-February offering alternative housing options (the class is investigating housing at Rider College for these classmates and their guests).</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/registration-hours</guid><title>registration-hours</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/registration-hours</link><description><![CDATA[Registration hours are:]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[registration]]></category><category><![CDATA[check-in]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Registration hours are:</p><ul><li>Thursday, May 22 | <strong>Noon - 11:00 pm</strong></li><li>Friday, May 23 | <strong>9:00 am - Midnight</strong></li><li>Saturday, May 24 | <strong>9:00 am - 10:00 pm</strong></li></ul><p>When you arrive on campus, Registration for the 25th will be in Whitman Courtyard. If you have been allotted a bed on campus, the housing check in is located at the Dillon Gym tent.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/park-car</guid><title>park-car</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/park-car</link><description><![CDATA[Parking is extremely limited, and attendees are strongly encouraged to use hotel shuttles, transit, or carpool when traveling to campus. For more information on shuttle service, accessible parking, and the Reunions Headquarters and Parking map, please visit the Parking and Transportation page of the Reunions website.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[check-in]]></category><category><![CDATA[locations]]></category><category><![CDATA[parking]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Parking is extremely limited, and attendees are strongly encouraged to use hotel shuttles, transit, or carpool when traveling to campus. For more information on shuttle service, accessible parking, and the Reunions Headquarters and Parking map, please visit the <a href="https://reunions.princeton.edu/map/">Parking and Transportation page of the Reunions website</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/post-p-rade</guid><title>post-p-rade</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/post-p-rade</link><description><![CDATA[As the 25th Reunion class, we will be near the head of the P-rade, right behind the Old Guard. After we march, the P-rade will continue for hours before the eating club barbecues and other activities commence.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[locations]]></category><category><![CDATA[p-rade]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>As the 25th Reunion class, we will be near the head of the P-rade, right behind the Old Guard. After we march, the P-rade will continue for hours before the eating club barbecues and other activities commence.</li></ul><!--- We encourage classmates to find a spot along the P-rade route past the “alumni arch” banner or relax inside our HQ area at Whitman College. Note that the class of 2024 will be positioned along the route near Whitman, and the area near the end of the route will be crowded. Alcoholic beverages will not be served at the HQs during the P-rade.-->
]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/what-sustainability</guid><title>what-sustainability</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/what-sustainability</link><description><![CDATA[Generating meaningful impact means a multi-pronged approach. Our class is striving to be more green on multiple fronts.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[sustainability]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Generating meaningful impact means a multi-pronged approach. Our class is striving to be more green on multiple fronts.</p><!--- **Reusable Cups.** We are minimizing the use of single-use plastic at our headquarters tent and related events by partnering with [TURN](https://turnus.in/), a leader in supplying reusable cups systems for events hosted by [Live Nation](https://turnus.in/blogs/as-seen-in/live-nation-to-introduce-reusable-cups-at-venues-and-festivals-a-major-step-toward-zero-waste-concerts), sports stadiums, the Daytona 500, and more. The 30th and 50th reunions are piloting TURN cups this year, as well, as part of an effort across classes to be more sustainable. **PLEASE RE-USE and RETURN orange TURN cups throughout the weekend and be a good example for other classes visiting our site.**-->
<!--- Pre-registered classmates and guests will also receive a branded 25th logo souvenir cup to use throughout the weekend and take home with them.-->
<ul><li><strong>Sustainable Swag Choices.</strong> We are reducing the environmental impact of apparel and swag by choosing higher-quality, classic-design items that are made of sustainable natural materials <!--(ex. Thousand Fell for shoes and Bella + Canvas for t-shirts) and less plastic “throwaway” items similar to conference tchotchkes, etc.)--></li><li><strong>Smart (& Delicious) Food Choices.</strong> Like many large event planners, we can reduce food related greenhouse gas emissions via menu planning (ex. substituting chicken and fish for beef for a few meals, as well as offering more vegan and vegetarian options as dietary preferences indicate). We’re also trying to reduce food waste sent to landfill by minimizing over-ordering via more practical food counts and looking to compost leftovers. Where possible, we are using wine glasses and metal flatware at meals and compostable plates for some HQ meals.</li><li><strong>Linen Rental Service for Campus Beds.</strong> The class is offering classmates who are staying in campus housing the opportunity to <a href="https://laundrysolutions.net/industries-served/summer-camp-linens/">rent bed linens</a> as an alternative to purchasing sheets and towels from the U-Store (which are often thrown away after the weekend, adding to textile waste and landfill usage, as many organizations do not accept donated bed linens). Linens can be rented at registration. The package is $30 for the weekend, and includes two sheets, a pillow and pillowcase, a blanket, two bth towels, and a washcloth. Alternatively, you can bring pillow/sheets/towels yourself. Princeton University is not offering linens for the 25th this year, but we felt it was important enough, for convenience and for environmental friendliness purposes, to pursue this on our own.</li><li><strong>Carbon Offsets.</strong> Using classmate donations received at registration, we are purchasing high-quality, quantifiable, verifiable carbon offsets after Reunions in order to help mitigate emissions associated with Reunions travel.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/childcare-options</guid><title>childcare-options</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/childcare-options</link><description><![CDATA[Princeton has partnered with YWCA Princeton to offer its traditional “Tiger Camp” childcare during Reunions Friday, May 23, to Saturday, May 24. We will share more details when we receive them from Princeton.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[children]]></category><category><![CDATA[childcare]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Princeton has partnered with <strong>YWCA Princeton</strong> to offer its traditional <strong>“Tiger Camp”</strong> childcare during Reunions <strong>Friday, May 23, to Saturday, May 24.</strong> We will share more details when we receive them from Princeton.</p><p>We will also be planning a host of activities at our Headquarters site for families with kids. <em>We are not legally allowed to provide child care onsite.</em></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://keepitfun.biz/faq/registration-changes</guid><title>registration-changes</title><link>https://keepitfun.biz/faq/registration-changes</link><description><![CDATA[Option A: Find your original registration email (subject: Reunions 2025 Confirmation). Scroll to the bottom. You should see one button for “View Registration Details” and one for “Update My Registration.” Use the “Update” button to make any changes.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:04:25 -0400</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Princeton 2000]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[registration]]></category><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li><strong>Option A:</strong> Find your original registration email (subject: Reunions 2025 Confirmation). Scroll to the bottom. You should see one button for “View Registration Details” and one for “Update My Registration.” Use the “Update” button to make any changes.</li><li><strong>Option B:</strong> Navigate to the Reunions registration site and log in with Tigernet. You should be able to update the registration from there.</li><li><strong>Option C:</strong> If you have tried both of these steps without success, capture a screenshot of the errors and email those to the <a href="mailto:princeton2000reunions@gmail.com">Registration Chair</a>.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>